https://www.armadafleetcommand.com/privacy-policy

Introduction
The site editor takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using Armada Fleet Command. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by the site editor, nor to persons that are not employees or agents of the site editor, or that are not under the site editor's control. Please take time to read this site's terms of use.
1. Collection of data
Registration of a user account on this site requires only a valid e-mail address and a user name that has not been used already. You are not required to provide any other information if do not want to. Please be aware that the user name you choose, the e-mail address you provide and other information you provide may render you personally identifiable, and may possibly be displayed on Armada Fleet Command intentionally (depending on choices you make during the registration process, or on the way in which the site is configured) or unintentionally (such as, but not limited to, subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party). As on many web sites, the site editor may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if it is the site editor's policy to display advertising) is set forth below.
2. Use of data
Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (ID 1033 0 1) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction a third party with or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates this policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on Armada Fleet Command to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.
3. Cookies
Like many web sites, Armada Fleet Command sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on Armada Fleet Command and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties serving the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site.
4. Minors
People aged thirteen or younger are not allowed to become registered users of this site. For more information, please contact the webmaster
5. Editing or deleting your account information
This site provides you with the ability to edit the information in your user account that you provided to during the registration process, by visiting your personal home page configuration page. You may request deletion of your user account by contacting the webmaster. Content or other information that you may have provided, and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within site forums, may continue to remain on the site at the site editor's discretion, even though your user account is deleted. Please see the site's Terms of Use for more information.
6. Changes to this privacy policy
Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the site, and or by a message being sent to the e-mail address you have provided, which is contained in your user settings.
7. NO GUARANTEES
While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, the site editor is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond the site editor's control that may result in disclosure of data. Consequently, the site editor offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or nondisclosure of data.
8. Contact information
If you have any questions about this policy or Armada Fleet Command, please feel free to contact the webmaster.
Birth Of The Federation
Last Post: Re: Why is torpedo accuracy so poor in BOTF?
Total Topics: 3538
Total Posts: 48839
Total Members: 19525
Newest Member: Footrot
Re: Why is torpedo accuracy so poor in BOTF? - slickrcbdRe: Supremacy new release - icemanRe: Supremacy new release - geordieRe: Why is torpedo accuracy so poor in BOTF? - kharilleRe: Supremacy new release - iceman
Visit: Birth Of The Federation
Armada
Last Post: Re: Civilization Series Favourite Scifi/Fantasy (incl Star Trek) TC Scenarios & Mods Hunt
Total Topics: 5914
Total Posts: 59837
Total Members: 15536
Newest Member: toffeeblue
Re: Civilization Series Favourite Scifi/Fantasy (incl Star Trek) TC Scenarios & Mods Hunt - blake00Armada 1/2 VS BOTF: Playing without CD - majorshanehelp with making this work in 1.2 - karriekittyRe: Dominus Galaxia (Master of Orion like game) - blake00Civilization Series Favourite Scifi/Fantasy (incl Star Trek) TC Scenarios & Mods Hunt - blake00
Visit: Armada
Sections:
Top of Page | Home
Armada 1 & 2
|
Armada Community Forums
|
ALL Armada Information
|
Armada 1 Downloads
3DS Max Downloads
Site Information:
About Us
|
Contact Us
|
Legal Notice
|
Privacy Policy
|
Terms of Use
ArmadaFleetCommand.com is the Star Trek gaming modding community for Star Trek Armada 1, Star Trek Armada 2, and Star Trek Birth Of The Federation titles.Trademarks are property of their respective owners.
Errors and omissions not intended.
Today's Stardate 2020.345 - Romulan Star Empire
